M - Model:
    Responsible for storing and management of data's project / code
    An example, store data from a online store, the model will be the
    correct part to do so, all the structure, what data will be used in the
    project etc, needs to be structured here at the Model.

V - View:
    Responsible for the interface of the project/code,
    part aligned as the name suggest related by the UI of
    the project.

C - Controller:
    As the name suggest will be responsible by the problems' heavier logics,
    like CPF validation (CPF - Unic Code Identification of Brazil, all the
    Brazil's born have one code that identify him as cityzen), in nutshell,
    the controller do the program's validations, verifications.

